Okay, I've doused a little bit of this sand trap with water because we got a nice dry, sunny day here.
Hitting out of wet sand is a little different because you're not able to get the loose sand underneath the ball as much.
So I don't have any great advice for you on wet sand because I want you to do what we've talked about and just practice out of it.
That's the best way to learn because the truth of the matter is, sand everywhere is different.
This is kind of brownish sand.
At Augusta National you'll see that beautiful white sand, and then all types of sand in between, and in different climates sand can be a little denser, or in the dry climates can be real loose because there's no moisture in it.
So when you have the opportunity to practice out of wet sand or if you're at a range, just moisten a part of the sand trap and work out of the wet sand.
You'll find it's very rewarding because if you were playing in a match and it just happened to rain the day before the sand could be wet.
So you tend to hit the ball, you can grab a little extra sand sometimes when it's wet but it's all different and that's why the sand is nothing that I can give you hardened fast rules on.
But the only rule I really need to give you is, you need to get a lot of reps around the sand because they've put sand traps in all golf courses and it's kind of a test.
So work on your wet sand play, and when you're confronted with it, it won't bother you at all where it might make your opponent get a little nervous.
So wet down the sand, get in there and practice out of it and you'll find that your skills will increase and you won't be fearful of virtually any lie that you could ever get.